joomshaper.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy - JoomShaper

### Introduction

Joomshaper.com values the privacy and security of the information seriously that you share with us through www.JoomShaper.com. We also want, you must feel comfortable using our website. It is important that you understand how we collect, use, and maintain your information. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our Terms of Use.

By using JoomShaper website, or using any JoomShaper products/services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy (last updated on May 24, 2018) and, as applicable, the [Terms of Use](https://www.joomshaper.com/terms-of-use).

### What types of data we collect

 **Personal Information** : It includes your name, address information, email address and URL, telephone number, account username and password, credit/debit card numbers and associated billing addresses (if intended to make a purchase) and expiration dates, account numbers, as well as other, similar information.

In case you use our support forums, we may additionally process data generated automatically your activity in the forum: date of last activity, subscribed threads, favorite posts, achievements in the forum, private messages and posts.

If you contact our technical support, we may process other data required to help you with any queries or support matters, such as login and password to Joomla administrator, FTP access, data collected in crash logs that are gathered by your CMS or the technical parameters of the server you use.  

Such information is only collected from you only if you voluntarily submit it to us.

In case you do not agree to provide us with the above-mentioned data, you will not be able to download our products and/or get effective support from JoomShaper.

**Non-Personal Information** : We gather statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website. This Non-Personal Data comprises information that cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information regarding, for example, user IP addresses where they have been clipped or anonymised, browser types and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our website.

### What purposes your data are used for

With the data stored on our site, we identify you as our customer/subscriber/patron and deliver products/notices and other marketing materials. As a visitor, you aren’t allowed to purchase any product or subscribe to newsletter or make a comment anonymously. So, these data are the only means to identify you and allow you to make these actions on our site.

### How long JoomShaper retains your information

When you register for a JoomShaper account, we process and keep your personal data we have about you for as long as you don’t delete the account/unsubscribe yourself (subject to laws and regulations).

### What we don’t do with your personal data

We do not and will never share, disclose, sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personal data to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services.

### Who has the access to your data

We don’t share your information like email, name, etc with third-parties (subject to laws and regulations). Only our administrators have access to your data. No third party can access to your data from us. However, you can review and delete your data whenever you want.

### What rights you have over your data 

Upon having an account on JoomShaper site, or leaving comments, you can request to have an exported file of the personal data we have about you. You can also request us to erase your data, excluding the data we are obliged to retain for administrative, security or legal purposes.

### Third party links on our site 

With regard to any third party links of products and services on our website, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.Third party sites have their own privacy policies.

### What policy we have for children

We recognize we have a special obligation to protect personal data obtained from children. We do not and will not knowingly collect personal data from any child under 16 without consent from their parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and are concerned about the transfer of personal data about your child, please contact with us.

### What our cookies do on your browser

JoomShaper site uses cookies to identify and track visitors, their actions of site, and their website access preferences. JoomShaper site visitors wishing not to have cookies placed on their browsers, should turn off cookies while using Joomshaper.com. In that case, you may lose some features of the website.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If in any case a breach of data such as loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure or access, personal data transmission, storage or otherwise processed happens, we will notify you immediately after we become aware of. 

### How you can review, update, get a copy or delete your data

You are free to review and update your information at any time directly through our site. To change your information please login to our site and click "My Account" link. If you want to delete or get a copy of your data on our site, send a mail to [[email protected]](https://www.joomshaper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1a696f6a6a75686e5a7075757769727b6a7f6834797577) . We will do that with immediate effect. 

### Newsletter

Don’t miss any updates of our new templates and extensions and all the astonishing offers we bring for you.  
We never spam
